<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Karl S Johnson</title>
        <link>http://karlsjohnson.com/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0600</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="http://karlsjohnson.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Setting up Hugo</title>
    <link>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20221207-hugo_setup/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0600</pubDate>
    <author>Karl</author>
    <guid>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20221207-hugo_setup/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<h2 id="setting-up-hugo">Setting up Hugo</h2>
<p>After 8 months, I am back posting on my website. Hopefully more will follow. I will be updating this post over the coming days to document my current setup for this website. I am using hugo install with homebrew on a mac.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Joshua Bush</title>
    <link>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220414-joshua_bush/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Karl</author>
    <guid>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220414-joshua_bush/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Joshua Bush Lost Palms Oasis Trail at Joshua Tree National Park in California.Map]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Sedona Mountains</title>
    <link>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220330-sedona_mountains/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 06:00:00 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Karl</author>
    <guid>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220330-sedona_mountains/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sedona Mountains Views from Hiking near Sedona, Arizona. Map]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Why Hugo</title>
    <link>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220329-why_hugo/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 07:59:48 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Karl</author>
    <guid>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220329-why_hugo/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Starting a Blog After not blogging for many years, I wanted to write again. The purpose is to help collect my thoughts and record the technical skills I am learning. Writing about it makes it easier to remember. A blog also allows me to keep learning, whether it is technical or photography skills. I wanted something easy to use at first. I could always switch to something else later. Now, I have been writing with Markdown for years.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Toadstool Hoodoos</title>
    <link>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220328-toadstool_hoodoos/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 09:59:48 &#43;0800</pubDate>
    <author>Karl</author>
    <guid>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220328-toadstool_hoodoos/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Toadstool Hoodoos Views from hiking on the Toadstool Hoodoos trail near Kanab, Utah. Map]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Starting the 3D Printer Journey</title>
    <link>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220325-3d_printer/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 09:59:48 -0700</pubDate>
    <author>Karl</author>
    <guid>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220325-3d_printer/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Starting the 3D Printer Journey Printer Head The two things that really inspire me are exploring and creating. Exploring can be traveling or doing something new, trying something out. Creating is about making something new. For me, this usually means either modifying something that already exists (improving) or building together something with exciting pieces. As a kid, I loved legos, and legos are how I think about creating. Legos pieces can be code, computer chips, or kitchen cabinets.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>First Post</title>
    <link>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220321-first_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 09:59:48 -0700</pubDate>
    <author>Karl</author>
    <guid>http://karlsjohnson.com/posts/20220321-first_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Welcome I am restarting my blog with two goals. The first one is to give me a digital presence in which to communicate to the digital world. The second is to help keep track of my goals somewhere. I have been writing to markdown files privately, but I wanted to start doing this publicly since most of the information might be helpful to others and not need to be kept secure.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
